Some criminals are made in prison
Shot Caller is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Ric Roman Waugh.
A newly-released prison gangster is forced by the leaders of his gang to orchestrate a
major crime with a brutal rival gang on the streets of Southern California.
Jacob 'Money' Harlon, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Kutcher, played by Omari Hardwick.
Frank 'Shotgun', played by Jon Bernthal.
Kate Harlon, played by Lake Bell.
Howie, played by Emory Cohen.
Bottles, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Shot Caller is a 2017 American crime thriller film
written and directed by Ric Roman Waugh.
The film chronicles the transformation of a well-to-do family man, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau, into a hardened prison gangster,
which he undergoes to survive California's penal system after he is incarcerated for his role in a deadly DUI car accident.
The film also stars Omari Hardwick, Lake Bell, Jon Bernthal, Emory Cohen,
Jeffrey Donovan, Evan Jones, Benjamin Bratt, and Holt McCallany.
It premiered at the Los Angeles Film Festival on June 16, 2017.
The film was released on July 20, 2017, through DirecTV Cinema and
theatrically on August 18, 2017, by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of prison, california, tattoo, murder, gun battle.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.